Okay, welcome after the break and let me
tell you about the events calendar. Today there are two
Nifty companies in the name of HDFC Life
Insurance and
Ambuja Cements. Ambuja Cements has
June quarter numbers but it is a
calendar year, so you will see the Q2
results, the latest June results,
ICICI Lombard, LNT Finance
Holdings and Polycap India. The cash market
numbers will appear on your screen.
Today the board will consider the Steel
Strip Wheels cash market counter.
Its results are there and that stock split has been
given quantum quality.
Preparations are being made to break one into five. Today there are
many important issues in the board, in which I will
tell you about some big ones
which will impact tomorrow. Technology, ₹10
adjustment of dividend, keep this in mind.
UK's unemployment rate, Eurozone's
inflation data, its housing
starts and building permits,
its results, but I am spoiling the sharp reactions. So
today there are more results in
Netflix, Johnson & Johnson, Novattis, Locke
Martin, this, hey, that giant tax is golden,
its numbers.  All the other numbers are already known.
Today the government is going to hold an all party meeting.
Union Minister
Nirmala Sitharaman and Jaishankar will brief everyone on the Sri Lanka crisis.
Regarding China and Shanghai, Neeraj's
concerns are highlighted again and again. Today, for
three days from today, that is, from 19th to 21st July, there will be Covid testing in 9
remote areas which are city districts
and that too
everyone has to be tested twice in three days.
This is how aggressive testing is being done to
prevent community spread.
Today, Ather's next gen 450x
electric scooter is being launched. This visual
on your screen is an old version of which
an update is going to come today. It will have a larger
battery pack. There will probably be more range. There may be a
powerful motor. Whatever updates will
come, the Vice President polls are today. The joint
position candidate is
discussing filing his nomination at 11:00 am. The meeting is another schedule.
Russian President Vladimir Putin is
going to Tehran today for Syria Peace,
so his queens, counterparts and
these two from Turkey will also be there.  Let's share in Meet,
in Maharashtra, Eknath Shinde fraction is probably forming
his National Executive,
Shinde and in the Election Commission today, that is the
display of his real C, so no wrong news,
12 MP today, let's see, today
Maharashtra politics is heating up again, in such a situation, while
talking about many events, I will
overdo it, all these important
events go, so show me, they will
open with pressure, but brother, there is a fall in
Nifty on the zone of 16150, there can be
a good opportunity again, in this way, that's all
in the morning call, a
direct deal beyond that
[Music]
but now is there anyone who can do it in the savings account